&gt；&gt；steve kinney：完成这个实际上是一样的，
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Getting this
done is effectively the same,
就像我们上次做的一样。
as what we did last time.
我们将制作一个可加载的注释视图组件。
We'll make a loadable note view component.
&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：在JS。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: At JS.
我实际上要从前一个做一个小的剪切和粘贴动作。
I'm actually gonna do a little cut and
paste action from the previous one.
因此，进口反应和可加载。
And so, import react and loadable.
我们将使用相同的加载组件。
We're gonna use the same
loading component.
就像我之前说的，你并不局限于一个加载组件。
Like I said before, you're not
limited to one loading component.
不同的UI具有不同的形状。
Different pieces of UI
have different shape.
也许它是一个旋转器，也许它是一个东西的骨架。
Maybe it's a spinner,
maybe it's a skeleton of a thing.
我会更多地定制我的装载机。
I would be a little bit more
customized with my loading ones.
但对于这个，我认为它会起作用。
But for this, I think it'll work.
在这种情况下，我们实际上要
In this case, we're actually gonna
带上NoteView，酷。
bring in the NoteView, cool.
然后，在NoteView容器中，我将把这个换成，
And then, in the NoteView container,
I'm just gonna swap this out for the,
&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：LoadableNoteView，酷。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: LoadableNoteView, cool.
让我们看看在这里的行动。
Let's take a look at
that in action over here.
我实际上要回到最初的页面。
I'm actually gonna go
back to the initial page.
我们可以继续。
And, we can go ahead.
我简要地看到了加载。
I briefly see loading.
我得到下一个组件。
I get the next component.
然后，我点击编辑，我逐步加载每个组件，因为我需要它。
And then, I hit Edit, I load each
component progressively, as I need it.
我之前提到的一些事情，但我想强调一点，是不是
Kinda thing I mentioned earlier, but
I wanna highlight a little bit, is that
IMPORT语法不是特定于REACT的，也不是任何特定的。
the import syntax is not react-specific,
it's not anything-specific.
我可以使用导入进行加载，只需load-dash，或者
I could have used the import for
loading, just load-dash, or
任何沿着这条线的东西。
anything along those lines.
你说你想导入什么文件。
You say what file you want to import.
你得到了一个承诺，无论默认是什么，它都可以解决，或者
You get back a promise that resolves
with whatever the default is, or
整个包裹都在那里。
the entire package is there.
所以这可能是，这些是反应成分。
So this could be,
these are reaction components.
这可能是任何东西。
This could be anything.
并且您不必使用React-Load。
And you don't have to use react-loadable.
你可以在任何你想要的地方使用这个代码。
You can use this code wherever you want.
所以我可以，例如，实现一个类似于，
So I could, for instance,
implement a feature which is like,
嘿，听着，我知道如果他们去了笔记视图，
hey, listen,
I know that if they went to the note view,
他们下一步可能会去找编辑。
that they're probably gonna
wanna go to the editor next.
所以当组件挂载时，我可以说组件挂载了，
So when that component does mount,
I can say component did mount,
导入下一个文件，提前启动。
import the next file,
kick that off beforehand.
有效地预取任何这些资产。
Effectively prefetching
any of those assets.
让我们来快速旋转一下。
Let's actually take that for
a spin real quick.
因此，我们将转到注释视图。
So we'll go to the note view.
我只想稍微进行一下重构，
I'm going to just slight a refactoring,
因为这是那些无状态功能组件之一。
cuz this is one of those
stateless functional components.
我们就在这里把这些都拿走。
We'll grab all of this right here.
我们会说，实际上坚持住。
And we'll say, actually hold on.
稍等一下，Class NoteView。
Give me one second, Class NoteView.
&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：Extensions React.Component。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Extends React.Component.
&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：放回render方法。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Put back
in the render method.
&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：是的，这就是为什么我变成了无状态函数，
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Yeah, this is why
I turned into a stateless function,
因为每隔[INAUDIBLE]，您应该使其成为无状态功能组件。
cuz every [INAUDIBLE], you should make
that a stateless functional component.
我就像，你离我远点。
I'm like, you leave me alone.
我们会说，组件DidMount。
We'll say, component DidMount.
在这里，这就是我们可以开始加载编辑器的地方，在这种情况下。
And in here, this is where we can actually
begin to load the editor, in this case.
所以我们会说，&gt；&gt；steve kinney：现在，
So we'll say,
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Now,
如果我立即需要编辑器代码，我可以说，我可以这样做，
if I needed the editor code immediately,
I could say then, and I could have,
如果是一个常规文件，开始使用它，在这里，我甚至可以使用Async Await。
if is a regular file, begin to use it,
and here, I can even use async await.
所以我可以说异步加载任何东西，并开始使用它。
So I can say async load whatever,
and begin to use it.
在这种情况下，我真的不知道。
In this case, I really don't.
这基本上就是一个预取队列，也就是，我说，嘿，
This is basically just a prefetch queue,
which is, I'm saying, hey,
如果他们加载了这个注释视图，他们可能会想下一步加载编辑器。
if they loaded this note view, they're
probably gonna wanna load the editor next.
那你干嘛不把那玩意儿卸了？
So why don't you kick off that load?
所以现在，希望他们不会看到任何加载时间，
So now, hopefully, they won't see
any load times, what so ever,
当它从无视图转到编辑器时，
when it comes from going from
the no view to the editor,
因为我们实际上已经提前开始了。
cuz we will in fact have kicked that off,
beforehand.
所以让我们继续，并尝试一下。
So let's go ahead, and try that out.
&gt；&gt；steve kinney：我们实际上将返回一个。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: We'll
actually go back one.
酷毙了。
Cool.
&gt；&gt；steve kinney：哦，有东西在生我的气。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Oops,
something is angry with me.
如果你不导出每个文件的内容，你会有麻烦的。
If you don't export stuff every file,
you'll get in trouble.
&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：支持默认注释视图。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Support
default Note view.
&gt；&gt；steve kinney：酷。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Cool.
所以我实际上要回到起点，
So I'm actually go back to the beginning,
并将在我们执行此操作时突出显示一些额外的工具。
and will highlight some extra
tools while we're doing this.
我一开始就提到，是的，很酷，
I mentioned in the beginning that,
yeah cool,
你在一台有快速互联网连接的昂贵电脑上，你就像，
you're on an expensive computer with a
fast Internet connection, and you're like,
对于我的用户来说，重150是一件很棒的事情，看看其中的任何一件是什么样子的。
it'd be great to be heavy in 150 for
my users, and see what any of that's like.
所以你可以在网络窗格中做什么，
So what you can do in the network pane,
实际上你可以模拟不同的网络连接。
is you can actually simulate
different network connections.
像快速3G，慢速3G和离线，并沿这些线添加一堆东西。
Like fast 3G, slow 3G, and offline, and
add a bunch of stuff along those lines.
实际上在表演部分还有一个，
And there's actually another
one in the performance section,
我认为这真的很强大。
which I think is really powerful.
您还可以调节CPU。
You can also throttle the CPU.
所以你想象一下在一个速度较慢的移动设备上是什么样子，
So you wanna imagine what it's
like on a slower mobile device,
你可以慢4倍或6倍慢，这是令人难以置信的酷。
you can go to 4x slower or
6x slower, which is incredibly cool.
只有在开发工具打开时才会出现这些情况，所以
And those will only be true
when the dev tools are open, so
如果你忘了关掉它，一切都会好起来的。
if you forget to turn it off,
it's gonna be okay.
但是为了说明一点，我想在这里做的是，我想改变这一点
But just to make a point, what I
wanna do here, is I wanna change this
也许再多一点，让互联网慢一点。
to maybe just a little bit more,
slow the Internet down a little bit.
&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：酷，所以我们正在加载。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Cool, so we're loading.
你可以看到，当我点击这个，它有点慢。
You can see when I click on this,
it's a little bit slower.
我们装了子弹。
We loaded it.
我们可以看到，我也加载了一些额外的捆绑包。
We can see,
I've also loaded some additional bundles.
当我点击编辑，它立即在那里。
When I hit Edit, it's instantly there.
我预取了编辑。
I prefetched the editor.
现在，这是正确的事情吗，你应该这样做，在每个组成部分？
Now, is that the right thing to do and
should you do it, in every component?
好的，如果你在[INAUDIBLE]数量的同时在每个单独的成分中做它，
Well, if you do it in every single
component while [INAUDIBLE] amounts,
你将有效地加载整个非洲[INAUDIBLE]他们要去的地方。
you will effective loaded the entire
Africa [INAUDIBLE] where they're going.
所以你必须对此有点[INAUDIBLE]，但是
So you have to be a little
[INAUDIBLE] about it, but
理论上，通过预取这些资产，可以减少一些加载时间。
you can theoretically reduce some of that
loading time, by prefetching those assets.
这不是一个特定的反应。
This is not a react specific thing.
这是您可以使用Webpack和许多其他加载程序执行的JavaScript操作。
This is a JavaScript thing that you can do
with Webpack, and a lot of other loaders.
但是，是的，你可以得到你需要的东西，这不在最初的捆绑包中。
But yeah, you can get stuff as you need
it, which is not in the initial bundle.
但是你可以开始，预取，这样看起来你没有这样做。
But you can then kick off, prefetching, so
that it seems like you're not doing that.
所以有效地，你得到了你的蛋糕，也吃了它。
So effectively, you get to have your cake,
and eat it too.
因为我做了，这就像世界变化对我们做的一样，对吧。
Because I do it, it's the same thing
as world change did for us, right.
去拿东西，准备好，在我们需要之前，
Going and getting the thing, and
getting ready for it, before we need it,
给用户一种瞬间的感觉。
gives that kind of
an instantaneous feel to the user.
在他们不需要的地方，我们减少了最低的时间，通过获得最初的
Where they don't have to, we cut down
on the low time, by getting the initial
捆绑较小，但我们最初支付的价格，这是对应用程序的响应时间。
bundle smaller, but we originally pay the
price, which is response time to an app.
因为现在我必须去拿它，特别是在一个较慢的连接上。
Cuz now I have to go get it,
especially on a slower connection.
但在这种情况下，使用预取，我们既可以缩短加载时间，也可以缩短加载时间
But in this case, with prefetching,
we can both shrink our load times and
缩短我们的响应时间，这真的，真的很酷。
shrink our response times,
which is really, really cool.
让我们去看看我们最终生产的捆绑包。
Let's go take a look at the bundle
that we ended up producing.
&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：我们希望看到的是又一个创建的捆绑包，并且
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: And what we hope to see,
is yet another bundle created, and
我们会得到一些关于我们最终做了什么的统计数据。
we'll kind of get some statistics
on what we ended up doing.
但是简单的说，我们实际上没有，如果你也包括我说的话，
But simply, we actually didn't,
if you also include me saying words,
我们并没有花很多时间来实现这一点。
we didn't spend a lot of
time implementing this.
然而，我们最初削减了三分之一的捆绑后，削减了十分之一
Yet, we initially cut down a third of
our bundle after cutting down a tenth of
我们的包裹。
our bundle.
使用代码错误以及使用它的组件成为它们自己的捆绑包。
Using a codemirror, and the components
that use it, become their own bundle.
我现在通过线路发送的实际主包是187千字节。
My actual main bundle that I'm sending
over the wire now, is 187 kilobytes.
对，这只是初始金额的一小部分。
Right, that is a fraction
of the initial amount.
有人想问我，那300千字节的目的是什么，
Somebody that tried to ask me for like,
what is the purpose of that 300 kilobytes,
只是沙子里的一条线。
it's just a line in the sand.
这只是一个目标，让每个块低于300千字节。
It's just a goal to get each
chunk under 300 kilobytes.
阿里亚奥斯马尼，实际上他的目标是设定为100千字节。
Aria Osmani, actually has his
goal set at 100 kilobytes.
对，这看起来是不可行的，但我们已经很接近了。
Right, which seems undoable,
but we've got pretty close.
现在我承认，这里没有太多东西可以剪掉了。
Now granted, there's not like
a lot left to cut out here.
我可以做，我可以做一些事情，比如触发它。
I could do it,
I could do something like trigger it.
我可能对我们的懒惰负载有反应，但我们现在正在尝试。
I probably get reaction about our
lazy load, but we're trying now.
但它真的很酷。
But it is kind of really cool.
我们能够相对快速和相当容易地看到显著的收益。
We're able to see significant gains
relatively quickly, and fairly easily.
然后，看看我们如何预加载和预刷新资产，
And then, see how we could preload and
prefresh assets,
使我们的用户有效地看不到这一点。
to make this effectively
invisible to our users.
&gt；&gt；steve kinney：请稍等。有点超前了
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: One moment.
Got a little ahead of myself in
那里的幻灯片。
the slides there.
好了我们回来了。
All right, we're back.
所以我确实想把这一点带回家，再多一点。
So I do wanna drive this point home,
a little bit more.
没关系，酷。
Which is okay, cool.
这是一个反应应用程序。
It's a react app.
但我有一个大角度的应用程序，或者任何类似的东西。
But I have a big angular app,
or anything along those lines.
或者琥珀色应用程序或主干应用程序。
Or an amber app or a backbone app.
所以，我觉得最初的几次我听到了所有这些懒惰的负载和
And so, I feel like the first few times
I heard about all this lazy load and
代码分裂，我就像，我不知所措，这永远不会发生。
code splitting, I was like, I'm
overwhelmed, this is never gonna happen.
我们重写一下，我会完全实现这一切。
We do a rewrite,
I'll totally implement all of this.
但是，我们可以看到我们所需要做的就是拿一个给定的组件，
But, we can see that all we need
to do is take a given component,
使用REACT LOADABLE之类的东西，并将其交换出去，对吗？
use something like react loadable,
and swap it out, right?
这是你可以去做的事情，你可以明天在你的应用程序中做。
This is something you can go, and
you can do tomorrow in your application.
然后开始弄明白，做捆绑，想象它。
And start figuring out,
do the bundle, visualize it.
最大的痛苦是什么，哪里是最痛苦的，对吧？
What are the biggest pieces of pain,
where's the most agony, right?
这可能不是最大的一个，但如果你知道，这是一个频繁
It may not be the biggest one in there,
but if you know that that is a frequently
装载一个或低挂水果，你可以明天实施这个。
loaded one or low hanging fruit,
you could implement this tomorrow.
而且不仅仅是具体的反应。
And it's not just react specific.
这是另一个[INAUDIBLE]网格。
This is another [INAUDIBLE] grid.
这是他们在实现这个之后分离出来的代码库。
This is their split out code base,
after they've implemented this.
还有一个骨干应用程序。
And there are a backbone app.
对，主要是放在提线木偶上。
Right, it's back on a marionette mostly.
骨干来自于这些奇特的工具出现之前的一段时间。
Backbone comes from a time before
any of these fancy tools existed.
所以如果他们可以在他们的应用程序中做到这一点，并且
So if they can do this with
their application, and
他们没花太长时间。
it did not take them very long.
所以你可以看到他们仍然有一个初始包。
So you can see that they
still have an initial bundle.
主束实际上是从左数第二个沿着顶部。
The main bundle is, actually that
second from the left at along the top.
所以他们现在立即加载D3。
And so they're now loading D3,
immediately.
他们现在正在立即加载jQuery，对吧。
They're now loading jQuery immediately,
right.
他们只是加载他们需要的片段来获得初始页面，然后作为
They're just loading the pieces they need
to get the initial page up, and then as
你四处导航，他们可以给你他们可能需要的所有不同的东西，
you navigate around, they can get you all
the different things that they might need,
所有不同的，比如SCSS文件。
all the different, like SCSS files.
如果他们确实需要jQuery或D3，可以获得这些。
If they do need jQuery or
D3 that can get those.
如果另一个包需要相同的包，那么您已经加载了它。
And if another bundle requires the same
one, you've already loaded it.
所以你并不是每次都交这种税，
So it's not like you pay this
tax of getting it every time,
它只是在逐步加载应用程序。
it's just progressively loading the app.
你记忆中的一切，都会留下来，所以
Everything you have in memory, stays, so
您不必支付网络负载成本。
you don't have to pay
that network load cost.
你可以降低你的初始负荷成本，
You get to cut down on
your initial load cost,
并且您可以减少最初的解析成本。
and you get to cut down on
your initial parsing cost.
所以所有我们试图解决的事情，在今天的课程中。
So all of the kinda things we were trying
to solve for, over the course today.
就像渲染一样，仍然是你需要处理的事情，
Like rendering, can still be
a thing that you need to deal with,
因为那就是你改变了世界。
cuz that's you changing the world.
但是，通过转移更少的代码，我们的代码更快，对吧，
But, by shifting less code,
our code is faster, right,
因为我们做的事情少了。
cuz we're doing less of something.
所以这就是可视化的一种。
So this is the kind of the visualization.
您可以看到它们的主包是39千字节。
You can see that their main
bundle is 39 kilobytes.
对，这就是他们通过线路传送的初始代码位。
Right, that's it for the initial bit
of code that they ship over the wire.
然后他们得到他们需要的碎片，缓慢但可靠。
And then they get pieces as they
need them, slowly but surely.